freesfx.co.uk 2018-11-12

# freeSFX.co.uk - Privacy policy

We are committed to protecting your privacy and to providing a secure and safe online environment. You can access and browse our Sounds without disclosing your personal data. However, you are required to provide your email address when creating your personal account to download or upload Sounds from our Website. We also require you to provide your email address when subscribing to our 'FreeSFX: Insider' service. 

This personal information is used solely for administration purposes and communication between ourselves and you. We will never trade, sell or distribute your personal details for any purpose or to any other party. Technical measures are in place to protect the personal information under our control against unauthorised access and modification.   

## Control of your personal information 

The personal information you provide to us can be modified by yourself at anytime, with immediate effect. This includes passwords that were created for access to secure areas of our website. Such modifications can take place from within your members account area. You can unsubscribe from our 'FreeSFX: Insider' service by clicking on the 'Unsubscribe' link in each email edition. We will delete your email address from our records immediately upon your request to unsubscribe. If you have a members account with us and have also subscribed to our 'FreeSFX: Insider' service, you can also unsubscribe via your account area. You may also email us at anytime and request to be unsubscribed from the 'FreeSFX: Insider' service at [hello@freesfx.co.uk](mailto:hello@freesfx.co.uk).

## Cookies 

Cookies are small, temporary text files that are downloaded to your computer's hard drive automatically by a website server and hold information about your online preferences. A website can only access the cookies it previously sent to your computer. Cookies are not harmful and cannot read data from your computer's hard drive. 

We use cookies only as a means of tracking user preferences and making your next visit more personal. They are not used for any other purpose. It is possible to turn off cookies in your internet browser's preferences and still use our website but it is recommended that you keep them enabled for a better online experience. 

## Disclaimer 

Freesfx.co.uk is not responsible in any way for the privacy policies or practices of any websites linking to or from this website. 

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
